ASHLEY STITH

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

□ ashley.stith@atozionwebdesign.com

202.681.3589

GitHub Profile

in LinkedIn

A To Zion Web Design, LLC

SUMMARY

Seasoned IT professional with over 15 years of software development experience with C#, Microsoft based platforms and tools, and modern frameworks, such as React.js, React Native and Angular.js. Has gained expertise in various .NET technologies within Federal and Civilian projects, across various domains. Applies technical expertise, strong attention to detail, strong development, and analytical skills to develop and manage intuitive, and easy-to-use solutions on schedule and on budget based on client specific business and technical requirements. Excellent communication and organizational skills gained in various diverse work environments. Versed in agile development methodologies (Scrum), as well as SharePoint and Power Apps.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Full Stack Web Developer / Solo Founder

A To Zion Web Design, LLC

June 2022 - present

- Remote, US
- Founded and operate A To Zion Web Design, LLC, a boutique web development, and design company
- Develop technical solutions to include simple web pages, complex and mobile responsive web applications, graphic design, and branding solutions
- Completed over 15 projects utilizing modern frameworks and technologies to include React.js, React Native, Angular, .NET and Canva
- Developed, published, and continue to maintain portfolio / company website-A To Zion Web Design, LLC

.NET Developer

Insight Global

III June 2021 - February 2022

- Quantico, VA
- Designed, tested, and developed 30+ custom components, classes, and APIs of a new crisis management application to be used by over 30k people daily using .NET and Angular
- Developed and executed test procedures for software components
- Planned, tracked, and managed deliverables on 20+ short-term sprints and additional future long-term deployments

.NET Developer

Global Dimensions

• Fort Belvoir, VA

Designed, tested, developed, and deployed 10+ custom web applications and features, integrating Microsoft tools with .NET, Web Forms, Workflows, JavaScript, and Web Services

SKILLS

C# / .NET / .NET Core

API (Rest / SOAP/ Web)

MS SQL, MySQL

HTML / CSS / JavaScript / jQuery

MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node)

React Native

Angular

Entity Framework / LINQ

Git / GitHub / ADS

Agile Methodologies

Microsoft Office

UI/UX Design

SHAREPOINT 2007/2010/ 2013/ 2016/ Online

ADDITIONAL SKILLS:

Testing, Bootstrap, Indexing, Reporting, Docker, Power Apps, InfoPath, MVC, ASP.NET, User Authentication, DevExpress, Visual Studio, VS Code

EDUCATION

Full Stack Development Certificate, 2021, George **Washington University**

Bachelor of Science Electrical Engineering, Minor Engineering Management, 2010, Old Dominion University Provided recommendations to Leadership for the development and improvement of systems and solutions

.NET Developer / Team Lead

Deloitte

Ctober 2016 – September 2019

Rosslyn, VA

- Oversaw the day-to-day operations of a 5-member developer team
- Designed, tested, developed, and deployed custom web applications, utilizing C#, ASP.NET, MVC, and MySQL
- Automated several business processes by integrating Microsoft tools with .NET,
 Web Forms, Workflows, JavaScript, and Web Services

Full Stack Developer

RGS Inc

August 2015 – September 2016

Crystal City, VA

- Maintained 5 systems and applications as Tier 3 support
- Automated several business processes by integrating Microsoft tools with .NET,
 Web Forms, Workflows, JavaScript, and Web Services
- Assisted with the planning, testing and implementation of a web server migration to a newer operating system version

Full Stack / .NET Developer / Business Analyst

Booz Allen Hamilton

□ July 2010 – August 2015

McLean, VA

- Served as Project Manager for several projects. Roles included: planning and documenting all aspects of the project and management of 3 junior developers.
- Automated business process by developing custom solutions that utilized Microsoft tools and Web Services. This included an application that fed into Oracle's Siebel CRM Technology

SECURITY ELIGIBILITY

US Citizen with Inactive DoD Top Secret SCI w/ CI Poly